A Guide to the Henry G. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA273
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Notes and Notebooks, 1949-1984; 3
  - Book #21- A1351 to A1449 [folder 1 of 2], August 9, 1973-January 7, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Book #21-A1351 to A1449 [folder 2 of 2], August 9, 1973-January 7, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Book #22-A1450 to A1523 [folder 1 of 2], February 9, 1977-August 27, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Book #22-A1450 to A1523 [folder 2 of 2], February 9, 1977-August 27, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Book #1-Dr. Kunkel, March 26-December 31, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Book #1-Dr. Kunkel, March 26-December 31, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5A)
  - Book #2-Dr. Kunkel, December 28, 1979-January 3, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Book #15, June 24, 1960-March 21, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Book #15, June 24, 1960-March 21, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 1A)
  - Book #16, March 22, 1962- (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Book #28, September 9, 1971-January 5, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Book #29, January 6-June 12, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Boston Data [folder 1 of 2], Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Boston Data [folder 2 of 2], Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Brooks-Book #24, June 1-October 20, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Case Report-Jacq. Hammond, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - C'-CTX-R. Vande Stouwe [folder 1 of 2], October-December 1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - C'-CTX-R. Vande Stouwe [folder 2 of 2], October-December 1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Chung, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Coating System", Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Complement Levels on Patients, September 1965-April 1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Complement Levels on Patients, April 1966-November 1967 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Complement Levels, November 1967-March 1969 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Complement Levels, March 1969-January 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Complement Levels, January-October 1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Complement [Levels] Book, October 1970-August 1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Complement Levels, July 1972-August 1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - C' Titus, Anti-C', July 1965-March 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Culture-Supernate Immunoglob, Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Data...., circa 1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Data. Drawer 7, 1973 and undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Data. Drawer 7. I. Includes "David's Results", 1976-1979, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Data. Drawer 7.II, 1980-1981, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Data. Drawer 7. II, 1980-1981, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8A)
  - Data. Drawer 7. III, 1968-1969, Undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Data. Drawer 9. "Hutchinson et al", 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Data. Drawer 9. Includes Data on Bloom's Syndrome, 1966-1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Data. Drawer 9. II, 1966-1970, Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Data. Drawer 9. III, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Data- 1)inhibition of MLC by 714, 715-2)...by all line supernates, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - [Data Summary-T Cells ], Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Dennis Brinkman, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Diversity, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Fenneke Joslin- [Book] A, January-June 1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Fenneke Joslin-[Book] B, June-October 1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Fenneke Joslin-[Book] C, October 1972-January 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Fenneke Joslin-[Book] D, January-March 1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Fenneke Joslin-Book E, March-June 1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Fenneke Joslin-Book F, June-September 1973 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Fenneke Joslin-Book G, September-November 1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Fenneke Joslin-Book H, November 1973-September 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - F.[Fenneke] Joslin-Book I, September 1974-June 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - F. [Fenneke] Joslin-Book J, July 1975-April 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - F. [Fenneke] Joslin-Book K, April-October 1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - F. [Fenneke] Joslin-Book L, October 1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Joshua A. Fierer-Lab Notebook #1, October 1969-May 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fluorescence/Routine Sera-Book IV, April 22-October 18, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Fluorescence/Routine Sera-Book V, October 21, 1963-April 28, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Fluorescent Techniques, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Formulae-Dennis Brinkmann-Buffers, Reagents, etc., Undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Gels, 1964-1969 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - General Notes, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Gm Typing, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Hbg-Charleston, 1955-1957 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Hbg-Italy, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Hbqs.Deus.Grad. Early DNA RA-2nd Book 11, December 26, 1956-July 31, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Hemoglobins 2-Book 9, September 1, 1955-April 10, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - H.K. [Henry Kunkel]-1B, March 1971-March 1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Immuno. #2- #460 UP 1001-Dr. Kunkel, February 1961-February 1962 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Immuno. #3-#1002 to___-Dr. Kunkel, February 1962-June 1963 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Immuno #4-H. Kunkel-31654 #2308, June 4, 1963-July 30, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Immuno. #5-#2309-#2882-H. Kunkel, August 1964-April 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Immuno. #6-#2883-#3516-H. Kunkel, April 1965-February 1966 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Immuno. #7- H. Kunkel, February-November 1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Immuno. #8- #4163-#4861-H. Kunkel, December 5, 1966-May 9, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Immuno. #9-H. Kunkel, May 1967-February 1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Immuno. #10-H. Kunkel, February 1968-September 1970 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Immunofluorescence-Book VI, April 1964-February 1965 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Immunofluorescence-Book VIII, February 10, 1966-August 23, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Immunofluorescence-Book IX, August 26, 1968-1974 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Immunological Studies on Lipoprotein-Zeph. Pres., 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Important Miscellany, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Intermediate Complexes, 1958-1960 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - I. Shepard, January 1958-February 1959 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - I. Shepard, February-September 1959 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - I. Shepard, September 1959-May 1960 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - I. Shepard, May 1960-May 1961 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - I. Shepard, May 1961-August 1962 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - I. Shepard, August 1962-December 1963 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - I. Shepard, December 1963-March 1965 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ishisaka Experiments, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Joan, 1976 &Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Dr. D. [David] Koffler, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Dr. D [David] Koffler-Antigens, Undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Anti-Sera, Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Data Book #2, March-September (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Data Book #3, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Data Book #4, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Data Book #5, 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Fluorescien Labeled Serums and Antidotes, Undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Frozen Tissues/Formalic Tissues (Back), 1966-1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Koffler-γG + γM Plates, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Dr. David Koffler- Immunofluorescent Data- Book #1, September 1966-February 1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Dr. D. [David] Koffler- Book I (Log), September 1966-January 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book II, February-March 1967 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book III, March-June 1967 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book IV, June-August 1967 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book V, August-October 1967 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book VI, October 1967-January 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler- Log Book VII, January-March 1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler- Log Book VIII, March-May 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler- Log Book IX, May-July 1968 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler- Log Book X, July-October 1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XI, October 1968-January 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XII, January-April 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XIII, April-June 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XIV, June-September 1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XV, September-December 1969 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XVI, December 1969-March 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XVII, March-May 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XVIII, June-August 1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XIX, August-November 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XX, November 1970-March 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXI, March-July 1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXII, July-November 1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXIII, November 1971-March 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXIV, March-June 1972 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXV, June 1972-January 1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XVI, December 1969-March 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XVII, March-May 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XVIII, June-August 1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XIX, August-November 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XX, November 1970-March 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXI, March-July 1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXII, July-November 1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXIII, November 1971-March 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXIV, March-June 1972 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXV, June 1972-January 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Dr. D[avid] Koffler-Log Book XXVII, June 1974-March 1975 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Log Book XXVIII, March-September 1975 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Log Book XXIX, September 1977-May 1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Ouchterlony Plates, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Photographs, Undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Dr. David Koffler-Procedures, October-December (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Serums and Antigens, 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Work Book #1 for Lydia, February-March 1967 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Work Book #2 for Lydia, May-November 1967 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Work Book #3, November 1967- (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Work Book #4, May-October (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Dr. [David] Koffler-Work Book #5, Undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - H. Kunkel-Book #26, February 16, 1971-May 25, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - H. Kunkel-Book #27, May 25, 1971-September 8, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - H. Kunkel-Book #30, June 15, 1972-February 24, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Dr. H. Kunkel-Daily Record #1- Workbook #14, 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Dr. Kunkel/Irene Shepard, 1960-1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Dr. H.G. Kunkel-Work Book #22, February-September 1969 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Dr. H.G. Kunkel-Work Book #23, October 1969-April 1970 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - [Lipids for Dr. Kunkel], 1948 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - List of Samples Recieved and Sent, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - [Loose Notes], Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Lymphocyte Culture-I-F. Joslin, November 1973-April 1974 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Lymphocyte Culture-II-F. Joslin [Folder 1 of 2], April-July 1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Lymphocyte Culture-II-F. Joslin [Folder 2 of 2], April- July 1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Lymphocyte Culture-III-F. Joslin, August 1974-September 1975 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Lymphocyte Culture-IV-F. Joslin, September 1975-April 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Lymphocyte Culture-V- F. Joslin, April-December 1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Methods-S. Litwin, Rockefeller Institute, July 1964- (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Microelectrophoresis [Technical Bulletins], 1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Mierozone-Book #2-A45 to A73, December 4, 1964-February 15, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Mierozone-Book #3- A74 to A126, February 17-July 19, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Mierozone-Book #4-A127 to A167, July 21-December 18, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Mierozone-Book #5-A168 to A202, December 1965-March 3, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975-1983 and Undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Cell Culture, Undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - [Miscellaneous Immunology Notes], Undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - [Miscellaneous Loose Notes], 1975-1977 and Undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - [Miscellaneous Loose Notes], 1981-1985 and Undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - [Miscellaneous Loose Notes], Undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - [Miscellaneous Loose and Untitled Notes], 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - [Miscellaneous Notes], 1969-1971 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - [Miscellaneous and Untitled Loose Notes], Undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - MLC HL-A 27 Work-C. Delaney and P. Wernet, March 15-May 16, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - [Monoclonal Antibodies], Undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Notebook: Rodes Trautman-Differential Refractometry-Vol. 4, 1954-1956 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Notebook: R. [Rodes] Trautman-Preparative Ultracentrifugation-Vol. 3, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Notebook: R. [Rodes] Trautman-Spinco E Plate Reading-Volume 2, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Notebook: Rodes Trautman-Ultracentrifuge Spinco E #85-Vol. 1, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Notebook: Spinco E 85 Run-R. [Rodes] Trautman-Book #5, November 7, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Notebook: Untitled [Final Program-Summer School Course, "Structure and Synthesis of Antibodies"-Villa Falconieri], 1966 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - [Notes, Drawer 2], 1967-1970 and Undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Notes, Drawer 2, III, 1966 and Undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Notes, Drawer 2, IV, 1969-1970 and Undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Notes, Drawer 2, V, Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Notes, Drawer 2, VI, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Notes, Drawer 5, Undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Notes-Drawer 7-I, 1980 and Undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Drawer 8-I, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Notes-Drawer 9, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Notes from Rodes on Comparator, Undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - [Notes on Journal Articles], 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Notes: 2 Peaks, 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Old Charts, etc....data, 1965-1967 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Oxytocin I-Isoelectric Point, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Oxytocin II, September-December 1952 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Paper Electrophoresis, 1953-1954 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Patients, 1952-1958 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Pevikon Blocks-Kunkel, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Phenol III, Undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - R.A.: 1st γ Glob. Heated Sheep Cell. End of Hbqs. Fe 59- Book 10, April 12-December 26, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Ralph E. Schrohenloher-#3, August 22, 1963 to December 20, 1963, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Reference Book [Folder 1 of 2], 1964-1975 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Reference Book [Folder 2 of 2], 1964-1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - References with Summaries-Rous Stories, Undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Rheum. Factor-Book 13, March 4, 1958-April 25, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Ripley, peps R., papain R. and L. Chain, Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Rosettes, June-August 1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Routine DNA Hemagglutination-Dr. D. [David] Koffler, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Routine Hemagglutination, November 1971-December 1974 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Routine, Ouchterlony #6-Plates #868-#1089-R.I. Carr, March 25-November 23, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Routine Ouchterlony #7- Plate #1090-Plate #1328, December 2, 1966-September 25, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Routine #15-Ouchterlony Book, November 18, 1969-July 6, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Routine #16-Ouchterlony Book, July 13, 1970-August 2, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Routine #17-Ouchterlony Book, August 2, 1971-February 28, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Routine #17-Ouchterlony Book, August 2, 1971-February 28, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5A)
  - Rulon Mayer Data, June-August 1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Sarcoid Book #1, 1957-April 1963 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Schur/ A. Corning, March 4, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Serum Albumin and Acetate Protein and Biuret, Undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Serum Lipid - Phenol Reagent, 1947-1948 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Serum Reaction, 1949-1950 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Serum Reactions III (End of Phenol Test- Chiefly Zephiran Reaction), 1947-1949 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - SLE & alpha- beta2 micro - Singer, #3, 1974 November-1975 February (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - SN4 EK Families - Krasenberg family, 1966, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted from scholarly access.
  - Some DNA - Rheum. f. Isolation- Double Az- Book 12, 1957 September 1-1958 March 4 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Special Items, 1957, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Standard Curves- H. Holman & H. Deicher, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Starch Block Electrophoresis Instructions, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sweden Exps., 1950-1951, 1957, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - T & B Cells: Misc. Notes, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Tetanus Toxoid, 1970-1974, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Tetanus Toxoid - raw data & loose materials, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Tetanus Toxoid II - Singer, #2, 1974 October (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Tetanus Toxoid, TT, 1970-1975, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Tetanus Toxoid, TT Experiments - FJ, 1974 September-October (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Restricted from scholarly accesss.
  - Tetanus Toxoid Screen- Singer/Gottleib/Joslin, #4, August-Sept. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - TT Screening II - Singer/Joslin, #5, October-November (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - TT Screening III - Singer/Joslin, #6, Nov.-Dec. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - TT Screening IV- Singer/Joslin, #7, 1974 December-1975 February (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - TT V - Singer/Joslin, #8, 1975 February-March (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - TT 7 - Singer/Joslin, #9, 1975 March-April (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Tissue Antigen Groups, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Ultracentrifuge Data- H.G. Kunkel Lab, 1952-1954 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Untitled Data Sheet - photocopy (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Untitled Loose Notes (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Untitled Notes (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Untitled Notes for Manuscript (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Untitled Notes & Graphs, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Urine Protein Book, 1968-1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Urine Protein CaL Book - Liling, 1971-1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Urine Proteins, 1962-1965 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - U-Starch, 1952, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Variable H, 1976, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Work Book - Dr. Koffler, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Workbook #3 - Dr. Henry Kunkel, 1961 March-1962 March (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Workbook #4 - Dr. Kunkel, 1962 March 15-1962 July 18 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Workbook #5 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1962 July 23-1963 February 14 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Workbook #6 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1963 February-June (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Workbook #7 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Workbook #8 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1963-1964 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Workbook #9 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Workbook #10 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Workbook #11 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1964-1965 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Workbook #12 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Workbook #13 - H. Kunkel, 1965 September-1966 January (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Workbook #14 - H. Kunkel, 1966 January-April (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Workbook #15 - H. Kunkel, 1966 April-September (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Workbook #16- H. Kunkel, 1966 September-1967 January (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Workbook #17 - H. Kunkel, 1967 January-August (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Workbook #18 - H. Kunkel, 1967 August 10-1968 November 22 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Workbook #19 - H. Kunkel, 1968 January-May (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Workbook #20 - H. Kunkel, 1968 May 28-October 21 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Workbook #21 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1968 October-1969 February (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Xeroxes - Individual Specs, 1969, 1970, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Zinc II Book, 1969 December-1973 February (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Zinc II Book, 1973 March-1979 August (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Zone Electrophoresis - Proc. Soc. Paper, 1951, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Zon. S04 albs., 1949 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - #II, 1960 May 5-1961 March 17 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 601, VKIII, VKIIIa, 1973, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Professional Activities, 1958-1983; 4
  Series 4: Professional Activities is arranged in the following subseries:
  Sub-series 1: Advances in Immunology. Sub-series 2: Conferences, Workshops, and Symposia. Sub-series 3: Journal of Experimental Medicine. Sub-series 4: Lectures and Manuscripts.
  - Advances in Immunology, 4.1
    - "Acute Phase Proteins with Special Reference to C- Reactive Protein and Related Proteins (Pentaxins) and Serum Arnylid A Protein." By M.B. Pepys and Marilyn L. Baltz- Vol 34, 1983 - Galley Proofs (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - "Acute Phase Proteins with Special Reference to C- Reactive Protein and Related Proteins (Pentaxins) and Serum Amylid A Protein." By M.B. Pepys and Marilyn L. Baltz- Vol 34, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Current, 1970-1979 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Expenses - Academic Press, 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Frances L. Owen - "T Cell Alloantigens Encoded by the IgT-C Region of Chromosome 12 in the Mouse", 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Front Matter, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Galley proofs - "The Biochemistry and Pathophysiology of the Contact System of Plasma," by Charles G. Cochrane and John H. Griffin - Vol 33, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Galley proofs - "The Biology of Monoclonal Lymphokines Secreted by T Cell Lines and Hybridomas," by Amnon Altman and David H. Katz- Vol 33, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Galley proofs - "Heterogeneity ofH-2D Region Associated Genes and Gene Products," by Ted H. Hansen, Keiko Ozato, and David H. Sachs- Vol 34, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Galley proofs - "Human Ir Genes: Structure and Function," by Thomas A. Gonwa, B. Matija Peterlin, and John D. Stobo - Vol 34, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Galley proofs - "Index," Vol. 33, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Galley proofs - "Lectin Receptors as Lymphocyte Surface Markers," by Nathan Sharon - Vol. 34, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Galley proofs - "Polyclonal B-Cell Activators in the Study of the Regulation of Immunoglobulin Synthesis in the Human System," by Thomas A. Waldmann and Samuel Broder - Vol. 32, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Galley proofs - "T Cell Alloantigens Encoded by the IgT-C Region of Chromosome 12 in the Mouse," by F.L. Owen - Vol. 34, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Galley proofs - "Typing for Human Alloantigens with the Primed Lymphocyte Typing Technique," by N. Morling, et al. - Vol. 32, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Galley proof - Advances in Immunology - Front Matter, Vol. 34, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - "The Generation of Diversity in Phosphoryl choline-Binding Antibodies," by Lee Hood, 1983 November (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Hans Spiegelberg - Vol. 35, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - "Hormonal Coordination of the Immune Response," by J. Comsa, H. Leonhardt, and H. Wekerle, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - "Human Ir Genes: Structure and Function," by Thomas A. Gonwa, B. Matija Peterlin and John D. Stobo, 1983 January (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - "The Human Thymic Microenvironment." By Barton F. Haynes, 1983 November (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - "Immunoglobulin RNA Rearrangements in B Lymphocyte Differentiation," by John Rogers and Randolph Wall - Vol. 35, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 13)